ocz.com 2019-02-24

# Privacy Policy

**Cookies:** We use cookies so we can provide you with the best possible user experience on our website. If you continue to browse without changing your settings, we’ll assume that receiving all the cookies on this Toshiba website is acceptable to You. You can also click the “I Agree” button to accept our policy in your browser so this message does not appear in the future. You can, of course, change your cookie preferences at any time via your browser settings. For more details of our use of cookies please see our Privacy Policy.[I Agree]()

Toshiba Memory America, Inc. ("TMA") respects the privacy of users who visit this website (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and share information we collect on this Site effective as of the date posted below. By using the Site and submitting information you agree to the terms of this Policy.

Information We Collect and How it is Used  
Access to Your Information and Opting Out  
Use and Sharing of Personal Information  
Cookies and Various Technologies  
Retention Period  
Sensitive Information  
Children's Privacy  
International Visitors  
Notification of Changes  
Protecting your Information  
Links to Third-Party Sites  
Your Comments and Suggestions

## Information We Collect and How it is Used

We automatically collect information when you visit the Site including your device’s IP address, and statistics about how you use the Site. 

We collect information that you submit when visiting the Site including product registration information (your name, email and postal address, telephone number, product information, and user name and password) or contact information if you sign up for our newsletter or contact us with an inquiry (email address, telephone number). If you submit a comment or suggestion or communicate with us through the Site we collect and retain the information you submit. 

We use e-mail links throughout the site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We try to read every message and reply promptly. Information in the message is used to respond directly to your comments or questions. We may also file your comments to improve the site and programs, or review and discard the information.

We may use your personal information to process your transactions, to contact you about products you have purchased, inform you of products and service opportunities that may be of interest to you and of new TMA updates or offerings, to conduct market research regarding Toshiba products or services, to customize the content of the Site for you, to support and enhance our communications with you, or for other general commercial purposes. 

## Access to Your Information and Opting Out

If you registered through the Site to receive our newsletters, you may change your email address and newsletter preferences on our Manage Your Subscription page, accessible via the emails you receive. You may opt out of receiving our newsletters or other marketing information from us by changing your preferences on our Manage Your Subscription page, if applicable, or by unsubscribing using the link on any email you receive from us. If you opt out of receiving our newsletters or other marketing information, we may still send you certain types of communications, such as product updates for your registered products, transactional or legal notification emails, warranty related communications and we may respond to requests from you by email. If you opt-out through one of these methods we will try to process your request in a timely manner.

Some countries allow you to request a copy of the information we hold about you. Requests can be made by contacting us through the “Contact Us” page, or emailing us at [PrivacyOCZ@taec.toshiba.com](mailto:PrivacyOCZ@taec.toshiba.com), and providing contact information and information that establishes your identity. We will endeavor to respond within 20 days of receipt of your completed request. In some cases we may charge a fee for providing this information.

## Sharing of Personal Information

We do not sell your personal information. We may share your personal information within the Toshiba family of companies for business purposes and with other companies who provide marketing or other services on our behalf and at our direction, but we do not permit them to use such personal information that we have shared for their own direct marketing purposes.

Your personal information may be shared with third parties that provide services to TMA (such as analyzing data, providing customer support, product registration, etc.), to the extent that such information is necessary for the provision of such services. TMA has contractual arrangements with these service providers under which these service providers agree not to disclose any information we provide to them. Other than such third parties, TMA will not share your information with anyone who is not an employee of TMA or an affiliate with a need to access the information for business purposes, or who has not signed an appropriate non-disclosure agreement except under the special circumstances provided in this Privacy Policy.

Your personal information may be shared with unaffiliated third parties under the following special circumstances:

(1) if you request or authorize it;   
(2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you;   
(3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); or  
(4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets). 

We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personally identifiable information, such as usage statistics of our Site or products, to our affiliates and third parties.

## Cookies and Various Technologies

We use technology to help us deliver customized visitor experiences and understand trends and patterns.

We may use or engage third parties to collect non-personal information using "cookies" and/or other industry standard technologies (e.g., clear GIFS, web beacons, pixel tags, javascript tag) to generate statistics or measure and analyze website activity (including page usage and paths followed during visits through our sites) in order to improve Site functionality, deliver content specific to you and/or targeted for your interests while using the Site and/or a third party web site, and to better manage advertising of our products. The collected data also helps us determine which product, service or support information may be appropriate for you. 

We may use temporary (“session”) cookies to grant Site visitors access to content and to enable commenting—actions they must be logged in to do. These cookies expire and are automatically erased whenever you close your browser. We may also use long-term (“persistent”) cookies to better understand usage patterns so we can improve the site for our customers. We use a persistent cookie to remember that you closed the cookie disclosure banner giving your consent to receive cookies, but this only works when cookies on our site are enabled. Persistent cookies usually have an expiration date in the distant future and remain in your browser until they expire or you manually delete them.

We may collect information about your online activities over time and also your activities on third party web sites. We do not respond to “do not track” signals, if any, being sent from your browser. We may permit select third parties to collect non-personal information about your online activities over time and across different web sites when you use the Site. If you would like to opt-out of any of the technologies that we and/or our third parties employ to collect your information via the Site (e.g. cookies), you may do so by blocking, deleting, or disabling them as your browser or device permits. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about your browser settings and how to handle cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of our site may not function properly.

For more information on third-party advertising-related cookies and how to exercise your choice to opt-out of them, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) and/or [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). Further general information about cookies and how they work is available at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

## Retention Period

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

## Sensitive Information

We ask that you do not send us or disclose any sensitive personal information (e.g., Social Security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Site or otherwise to us.

## Children's Privacy

This Site is not directed to or intended to be used by children under the age of 18. TMA does not knowingly collect personal information about children through the Site. If you are under the age of 18, please do not provide any personally identifiable information to us through this Site.

## International Visitors

This Site is operated in the United States of America and information you submit through our Site is stored on servers located in the United States. If you are visiting from a location outside the United States, your information may be processed by us in the United States, where laws regarding data protection may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By using this Site and by providing any personal information to the Site, all users, including without limitation users in Canada and the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States.

## Notification of Changes

From time to time, we may choose to change our Privacy Policy. We will notify you of material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting a revised Privacy Policy on the Site with an updated effective date. Any updates, revisions, supplements, modifications or amendments to this Privacy Policy shall be effective immediately upon its posting. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site and your continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

## Protecting your Information

We have implemented reasonable physical, electronic and administrative security measures and practices in an effort to protect the security, integrity and confidentiality of your personal information. However, no security system is 100% secure. It may be possible for third parties to intercept or access information that you provide to TMA or its third party service providers. We cannot guarantee the security of your information, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your personal information. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the "Contact Us" page. 

## Links to Third-Party Sites

When you use the Site, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control. These may include sites where you register products that you have purchased. We may also allow third-party sites or applications to link to the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites except where specifically stated, but we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to our Site. 

We always appreciate hearing from you and welcome your comments and emails. But we ask that you exercise good judgment because material we receive will be considered public and non-confidential. Additionally, we reserve the right to use any comments and emails you share without limitation. You may contact us through the “Contact Us” page or email us at [PrivacyOCZ@taec.toshiba.com](mailto:PrivacyOCZ@taec.toshiba.com).

OCZ is a trademark or registered trademark of Toshiba Memory Corporation and/or its affiliates. All third party trademarks are the properties of their respective owners.
